{"question":"5  +  -2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3  -  6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-3","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-17  +  18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-16  -  -2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-14","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17  +  17 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"34","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-13  +  14 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-16  +  -2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-18","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-1  +  -15 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-16","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15  -  -7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"22","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-3  -  19 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-22","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3  -  12 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-9","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3  +  1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11  +  -10 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17  +  17 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"34","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-17  +  -14 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-31","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19  -  -5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"24","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"19  -  -13 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"32","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0  +  0 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"0","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-12  -  -19 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1  -  0 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15  +  -11 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0  +  1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-12  +  14 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"2","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9  +  -6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7  -  1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"6","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15  -  -1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14  -  -9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"23","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5  +  3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-11  +  10 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15  -  3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-8  -  18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-26","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4  -  -6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-1  -  17 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-18","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7  +  5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11  +  1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4  -  -16 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"20","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-8  +  -5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-13","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18  -  6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-15  +  -11 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-26","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-15  -  16 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-31","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2  +  -11 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-9","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-5  -  5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-10","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8  +  -3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"5","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-13  +  -17 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-30","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-2  -  -10 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-19  -  8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-27","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-8  +  -3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-11","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-11  +  -9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-20","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-19  -  10 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-29","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-16  +  13 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-3","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1  -  -3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0  +  -6 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-6","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-13  -  19 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-32","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-16  +  -7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-23","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2  -  -8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"10","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15  +  -8 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14  -  2 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"12","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-16  -  12 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-28","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10  +  13 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"23","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-2  +  -17 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-19","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-5  -  19 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-24","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9  -  -7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"16","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14  +  -5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"9","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-15  -  -18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"3","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4  +  3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"7","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18  -  3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"15","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-10  -  -18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6  -  16 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-10","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-10  -  -18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"8","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-17  +  13 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-4","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-13  -  18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-31","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-4  -  7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-11","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-8  -  -5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-3","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-9  +  9 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"0","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-7  +  1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-6","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"17  -  -19 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"36","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16  -  -1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"17","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0  +  -1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1  -  -3 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"4","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14  +  19 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"33","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12  -  -16 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"28","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5  +  16 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"21","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-16  +  -5 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-21","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6  -  -11 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"17","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-15  -  -14 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3  +  -11 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-8","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-15  +  -1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-16","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-19  -  -1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-18","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15  -  -13 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"28","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-15  -  -1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-14","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-12  -  -4 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-8","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-13  +  12 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-1","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14  -  -19 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"33","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-5  +  18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"13","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-11  -  14 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-25","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"13  +  1 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"14","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0  +  -7 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-7","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"11  +  -15 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-4","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"-13  +  -10 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-23","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"15  +  -18 \u003d ?","answers":[{"value":"-3","hint":"Ответ?"}]}
